[
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word possessiveness.",
        "answer": "ssenevissessop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word feeddoor.",
        "answer": "rooddeef"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word walloonness.",
        "answer": "ssennoollaw"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word rooffoot.",
        "answer": "tooffoor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word aarrgghh.",
        "answer": "hhggrraa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word cookkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkooc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word balloonnookkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkoonnoollab"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word sheeppoodle.",
        "answer": "eldooppeehs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word hoddy-doddy.",
        "answer": "yddod-yddoh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word chattahoochee.",
        "answer": "eehcoohattahc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word colleenness.",
        "answer": "ssenneelloc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word toolleen.",
        "answer": "neelloot"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word sweettoothed.",
        "answer": "dehtootteews"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word reentered.",
        "answer": "deretneer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word toollooter.",
        "answer": "retoolloot"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word spoonnookkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkoonnoops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word engineering.",
        "answer": "gnireenigne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word spookkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkoops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word cheerlessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselreehc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word whippoorwill.",
        "answer": "lliwrooppihw"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word tallahassee.",
        "answer": "eessahallat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word goossee.",
        "answer": "eessoog"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word abracadabra.",
        "answer": "arbadacarba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word successfully.",
        "answer": "yllufsseccus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word tattooee.",
        "answer": "eeoottat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word sleeplessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselpeels"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word barrenness.",
        "answer": "ssennerrab"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word interroommate.",
        "answer": "etammoorretni"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word senescence.",
        "answer": "ecnecsenes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word rottenness.",
        "answer": "ssennettor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word wheelloose.",
        "answer": "esoolleehw"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word possession.",
        "answer": "noissessop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word cookkoo-oosee.",
        "answer": "eesoo-ookkooc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word hopelessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselepoh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word rookkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkoor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word feoffee.",
        "answer": "eeffoef"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word deerreeve.",
        "answer": "eveerreed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word bookkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkoob"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word commotion.",
        "answer": "noitommoc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word yellowwooddom.",
        "answer": "moddoowwolley"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word heedlessness.",
        "answer": "ssensseldeeh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word uselessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselesu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word meseems.",
        "answer": "smeesem"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word endlessness.",
        "answer": "ssensseldne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word defenselessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselesnefed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word keenness.",
        "answer": "ssenneek"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word referee.",
        "answer": "eerefer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word listlessness.",
        "answer": "ssensseltsil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word addressee.",
        "answer": "eesserdda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word aggressiveness.",
        "answer": "ssenevissergga"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word woodenness.",
        "answer": "ssennedoow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word entente.",
        "answer": "etnetne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word boobbook.",
        "answer": "koobboob"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word occurrence.",
        "answer": "ecnerrucco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word homelessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselemoh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word hooffoot.",
        "answer": "tooffooh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word stubbornness.",
        "answer": "ssennrobbuts"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word sleeveless.",
        "answer": "sseleveels"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word beerroom.",
        "answer": "moorreeb"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word successlessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselsseccus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word deeppool.",
        "answer": "looppeed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word selflessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselfles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word voorraaddoosspullen.",
        "answer": "nellupssooddaarroov"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word wooddeer.",
        "answer": "reeddoow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word wooddoor.",
        "answer": "rooddoow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word supposititious.",
        "answer": "suoititisoppus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word tennessee.",
        "answer": "eessennet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word unsuccessfully.",
        "answer": "yllufsseccusnu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word daybookkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkoobyad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word subcommittee.",
        "answer": "eettimmocbus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word woolloom.",
        "answer": "moolloow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word roommood.",
        "answer": "doommoor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word kookkee.",
        "answer": "eekkook"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word inconcoction.",
        "answer": "noitcocnocni"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word deterrent.",
        "answer": "tnerreted"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word committee.",
        "answer": "eettimmoc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word agelessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselega"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word steellook.",
        "answer": "koolleets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word floorroof.",
        "answer": "foorroolf"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word insensibleness.",
        "answer": "ssenelbisnesni"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word aallaakh.",
        "answer": "hkaallaa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word suddenness.",
        "answer": "ssenneddus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word alfalfa.",
        "answer": "aflafla"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word sullenness.",
        "answer": "ssennellus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word raccoonness.",
        "answer": "ssennooccar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word belleekkeeper.",
        "answer": "repeekkeelleb"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word lawlessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselwal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word appropriate.",
        "answer": "etairporppa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word sleeplessness.",
        "answer": "ssensselpeels"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word sweettooth.",
        "answer": "htootteews"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word steelloops.",
        "answer": "spoolleets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word accessible.",
        "answer": "elbissecca"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word tattletale.",
        "answer": "elatelttat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word coolleearlee.",
        "answer": "eelraeellooc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word greenness.",
        "answer": "ssenneerg"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word senselessly.",
        "answer": "ylsselesnes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word mississippi.",
        "answer": "ippississim"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word flooddoorroom.",
        "answer": "moorrooddoolf"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word taattoo.",
        "answer": "oottaat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please reverse the word roommeet.",
        "answer": "teemmoor"
    }
]